PROFILE

An efficient MERN stack web developer with an intuition for both system and UI design. Adept in improvising and adapting to challenges, with a proclivity to constantly optimize using creative approaches. Very research-oriented and thorough in her methods. Would like to bring her passion to any organization that appreciates it and presents ample intellectual challenges.

PROJECTS

Lint 🛮

Github 🛮

Fullstack ecommerce website for apparels and lifestyle products. A collaboration of 4 members - built and executed in 5 days.

Features:

- Login/Signup, sticky & fully functional navbar, landing page
- Dynamically generated products page
- Product detail page, toggle pictures, cart popup, cart page
- Pagination, responsiveness, filtering, admin panel

Areas of Responsibility:

- Led the team, delegated tasks, monitored progress, planned the workflow
- Conducted daily meets, assisted team mates
- ullet Created the backend rest API along with proper documentation $\ensuremath{ riangle}$
- Built cart feature, worked on responsiveness of the whole website

Tech Stack: ReactJS | Chakra UI | Redux | NodeJS | MongoDB | ExpressJS | Mongoose

Oasis 🖪

Github 17

Ecommerce website for multipurpose products.

A collaboration of 4 members - built and executed in 5 days

Features:

- Admin and user authentication, product carousels
- Sorting, filtering, pagination
- Cart, wishlist (user dynamic)
- Admin panel with all CRUD functionalities, searchbar, pagination, responsiveness & dark mode support

Areas of Responsibility:

- Built admin panel, acclimated to using typescript with NextJS, redux and Chakra UI
- · Assisted in acquiring data

Tech Stack: NextJS | Chakra UI | Redux | Typescript | JSON Server

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer, Revly □

05/2023 - present | Bangalore, Karnataka

- Built their fully responsive website with dynamic elements, integrated SDKs for analytics and contacting leads.
- Learnt Svelte and added features and enhancements in their SDK.
- Acquired understanding of NestJS and TypeORM and built APIs, DTOs, CRON schedulers, automations and wrote complex SQL queries and logic.
- Used class validator and OOP to create complex settings with critically validated forms in their dashboard.
- Grasped Twilio services and built features like full-fledged Chat with media support, notification and links, note taking, offline calling and automated messaging, etc. to enhance their video calling app.
- Provided dynamic solutions and optimised code and workflow to ensure minimal future modifications.

Tech Stack: ReactJS | NestJS | TypeORM | Svelte | Material UI | Tailwind CSS | SQL

Intern, Shankus Medicity (Paediatric Neuro Center) ☑ 10/2019 - 11/2019 | Mehsana, Gujarat

• Conducted psychological mapping, audits & training; built protocols.

Madhurima Poddar Full Stack Web Developer



RimRaider639 R Portfolio

in Madhurima Poddar

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development, Masai School ☑ 08/2022 - 04/2023

Bachelors of Computer Applications, Amrita Vishwa Vidyapeetham 07/2021 – present | Coimbatore

A Levels, Divine Child International School 04/2019 - 03/2021 | Ahmedabad

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JS | TS | ReactJS | Svelte | NextJS NestJS | Chakra UI | Material UI | HTML CSS | TypeORM | DSA | Redux | Testing Class Validator | Python | JAVA | OOP SQL | ML | Web Scraping | Data Science **Computer Vision**

SOFT SKILLS

Research | Organization | Critical Thinking Resourcefulness | Creativity

ACHIEVMENTS

Certified in Astronomical Data Science, Spartificial 🛮

Machine Learning for Physics Application, Spartificial

Complete Python Bootcamp, *Udemy*

Led the 3rd Top Team - Lunathon (Hackathon), Spartificial with ISRO ♂

Sketching & Painting | Programming Games Building ML/DL Models | Brain Science